this is the new squid Games 2 meal from
McDonald's and there's an item in here
that's got me really excited the meal
comes with a drink some fries a Big Mac
and an actual dalona candy people have
literally died for this it comes in four
different shapes and they've actually
replaced the umbrella with the
McDonald's symbol the tin actually looks
like from the show let's have a look
what we got oh we got the triangle we
ain't dying today there one thing the
shows told me is that saliva is your
best friend here but I wet the PIN and
try and just scrape this thing out and
hopefully we can get through it well
actually tastes amazing I think with the
triangle you can even just break off the
edges ooh look how thick it is it's
going to take me forever if I just get
these edges here and break it there we
go okay I think we're close one more I
think we gone and beaten the squid games
let's go